Clerk: OK.
Vickey: BOY,
Maniac:
Vickey: come on, y'all.
Diane: Sean, y'all
Vickey: definitely
Radio DJ:
Sean: dee.
Sean: muthafuckas.
Saying this if I didn't
need this job
for this halfway house.
Man on radio: LARGE FRY?
00.
Antoinette:
I got 400-500
$500?
For $500...
With the gold ds on it.
Sportscaster:
Sean: all right.
Dee Loc:
Vickey:
Dee loc: yeah!
Television: the hawks
Radio: west side radio
OK.
OK?
77, 78, 79--
Dee: can you
Computer voice:
5...5...
3...7...5...fo'.
Computer voice: AGAIN.
Operator: we're sorry--
Wayne: you sold me
Mickey: see, that's what
Puffy got 2 "fs" in it,
Face, on phone:
Sean: that's what I been
Face: don't forget about
all: Oh, here he comes.
Woman: this the good stuff?
Sean: mmm. Damn, baby.
Michelle:
Dee loc: hey, babies!
Sean: oh, shit!
Dee Loc:
Antionette:
Dee loc: man, enough
Man, 50,000, dog.
Hang up, hang up.
To 911?
Trey Dee:
Slim:
Slim: ahem, ahem.
Face: hey, trey dee,
Dawg: he needs
Face: don't be no hero.
OK.
Slim: yeah, she callin'
Face: man,
Radio: OK, that's
Director: all right, cut, cut.
Woman: it's on